Subtitle By: explosiveskull
& Improved By: Fidel33
Sub Upload Date: July 22, 2018
(DISTANT CHANTING)
- Okay?
- Yeah.
(CROWD SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(COMMENTATOR SPEAKING THAI)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (CROWD SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
- (BOTH GRUNTING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
(SPEAKING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (BELL DINGS)
- (SHOUTING CONTINUES)
(SHOUTING STOPS)
(CROWD CHEERING)
- (SPEAKING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
- No, no, no.
I want to fight! I have to fight.
I have to fight.
(CROWD GASPS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
- You got the money?
- Yeah, man.
Thanks.
(MAN SHOUTING IN THAI)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
(COUGHS)
(BANGING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTS)
(SHOUTING IN THAI)
Okay.
(ALL CONTINUE SHOUTING
IN THAI)
(GRUNTING)
I don't speak Thai. I don't...
I don't know
what you're saying,
I don't know what
you're sayin'.
I don't know
what you're fucking saying,
I don't understand.
- (SHOUTING IN THAI)
- (GROANING)
(OFFICERS SPEAKING THAI)
(GROANING)
(SIREN WAILING)
(OFFICER SPEAKING THAI)
(COUGHS)
(SPEAKING THAI)
(GUARDS SPEAKING THAI)
(PRISONERS CHANTING
IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(GUARDS SPEAKING THAI)
Yeah.
Yes.
(GUARDS CONTINUE
SPEAKING THAI)
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
(CAMERA CLICKS)
(GUARD SPEAKING ENGLISH)
Hmm?
(INAUDIBLE)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CHATTER CONTINUES)
(IN ENGLISH)
Hey, you okay? Hey.
(SPEAKING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(IMITATES SMOKING HEROIN)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
(WHISTLES BLOWING)
(GUARD SPEAKING
IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
- (ALL AGREE)
- (CONTINUES IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(ALL CLAMORING)
Get off me!
Fuck off! Fuck off!
You fucking around with me?
I'm going to fuck you up.
You want to fucking fight?
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
(PRISONERS AGREEING)
(GUARD CONTINUES SPEAKING
IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(PRISONERS WHOOPING)
(PRISONER SPEAKING THAI)
(ALL CONVERSING IN THAI)
(BOTH SPEAKING THAI)
- Billy.
Billy.
- Moore.
- Billy Moore.
Billy Moore... Moore.
- (PRISONERS LAUGH)
- Yeah.
- Yaba? You said Yaba?
(ALL LAUGHING)
- BILLY: No.
- No?
- Boxer. Boxer.
- Boxer?
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
(IMITATES FELLATIO)
(PRISONERS LAUGHING)
Yes, I understand.
No. No cock.
- No cock.
- No more.
- (ALL LAUGH)
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
One...
(ALL SHOUTING)
Hey! Okay, okay, okay...
(PRISONERS CHATTERING)
(PRISONER SPEAKING ENGLISH)
(ALL SHOUTING ENCOURAGEMENT)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Stop it, man. Fuck's sake.
What are you doing man?
Don't fucking touch me!
Fuck off!
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
No, no. I stay here.
I stay here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
(PRISONERS LAUGHING)
(STRUGGLING)
(SPEAKING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(BILLY GRUNTING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROANING)
(SHOUTING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(WHIMPERING)
(IN ENGLISH)
Okay? You.
- (BANGING ON DOOR)
- (WHISTLES BLOWING)
(SPEAKING THAI)
I need painkillers.
What do you mean,
you don't have?
You're an infirmary.
I was told you did
tramadol for free.
What do you mean,
it's not free?
I've just seen you give it
to five people in a row.
No, I've got no money.
I've got no money.
I've been told it's free.
No, I don't have no...
I have no cigarettes, okay?
I've got no...
I have got no,
and I just want tramadol.
This is not right. Give me...
No, fuck you, man.
- (SPEAKS IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
- (PRISONERS SHOUTING)
- (GRUNTING)
- (WHISTLE BLOWING)
(ALARM BLARING)
(SHOUTING IN THAI)
Eh? Who wants
to fucking go next?
Who wants to fucking go next?
(YELLING)
(SHOUTING IN THAI)
(GUARDS SPEAKING THAI)
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(INAUDIBLE)
(PRISONERS CATCALLING)
(IN ENGLISH)
You love ladyboys!
Hey.
Yes.
Do you remember me?
I just wanted to
say thank you
for the other day.
For helping me when,
when I was in a bad way.
Okay.
And I wanted
to ask as well if I...
If I could get
some cigarettes?
I've got no family.
I'm going to get some money
next week, okay?
In my account.
I just need you borrow me
some cigarettes,
and I'll pay you back.
Red ones.
Billy.
What's your name, by the way?
Nice to meet you, Fame.
Uh, can I just get
one more packet, please?
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
(SPEAKING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
- (GUARD SHOUTING)
- (PRISONERS SHOUTING RESPONSE)
(ALARM BLARING)
(WHISTLES BLOWING)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
(ALL SPEAKING
IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(IN ENGLISH)
- (WHISTLES CONTINUE BLOWING)
- (ALARM BLARING)
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
(SPEAKING THAI)
It's not mine.
(SPEAKING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
Look. Look, this is mine.
That's mine. That's my top.
That's my top. That's
not mine, I swear to God.
- (CONTINUES IN THAI)
- That's not my shirt!
That's fucking not mine!
Look, it doesn't even fit.
It doesn't even fucking fit.
Look, it's fucking too small.
(SPEAKING THAI)
It's not mine.
I promise you, it's not mine.
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
(PRISONER SHOUTING OVER PA
IN THAI)
- (FLOG SMACKING)
- (PRISONER SCREAMING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
Hey.
- Later.
- Heroin?
Later.
(SPEAKING THAI)
- (ALARM BLARING)
- (WHISTLES BLOWING)
(IN ENGLISH)
(SPEAKING THAI)
Yaba?
It's my yaba.
- Huh?
- My yaba.
It's from a ladyboy.
(BILLY BREATHING DEEPLY)
You've got the stuff, man?
Fuck you!
Fuck you, man!
Where is your fucking
heart, man?
Where is your fucking heart?
I'm not gonna beat up some
fucking Muslims, all right?
I'm not fucking scared!
I'm not fucking scared.
I don't give a fuck about that
I'm not scared.
I'll fucking beat up everyone
in this fucking prison,
if I have to.
I'm saying to you,
I just need a hit now.
If you fucking give me
a hit now,
I'll fucking do whatever
you want, man.
I'll do what ever
you fucking want.
(INAUDIBLE)
(BILLY GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GUARD SPEAKING ENGLISH)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SOBBING)
(SPEAKING THAI)
(PRISONER SPEAKING THAI)
(SHOUTING IN THAI)
(BILLY BREATHING SHAKILY)
(MAN SPEAKING THAI ON PA)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(IN ENGLISH)
(SPEAKING THAI)
(TRADITIONAL MUSIC PLAYING)
- (GUARD SHOUTING)
- (PRISONERS SHOUTING RESPONSE)
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
(MEN GRUNTING)
I want to train.
Hey.
(SPEAKING THAI)
I want to box.
I'm a boxer. I can show you.
I can fight.
I need to fight.
Let me in!
(SPEAKING THAI)
Come on, just...
Just let me show you.
All right?
Same, same. I'm a boxer.
(SPEAKING THAI)
Come on, man, let me in...
(SHOUTS)
(CONVERSING IN THAI)
BILLY: Hey.
How are you?
Look, I'm sorry about not
bringing the cigarettes back.
I've had a fucking rough time.
I was wondering maybe if I can
get some more cigarettes,
join the boxing team.
I wanna fight again.
Just give me this one chance,
and I promise you
I'll fucking pay you back.
I swear to God, Fame.
I'll prove to you.
(SPEAKING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
I'll make it up to you.
(MEN GRUNTING)
Hey. Hey!
I got these for you.
(SPEAKING THAI)
(MEN CONTINUE GRUNTING)
Come.
- COACH: You okay?
- Okay.
(COACH SPEAKING THAI)
- (BOTH GRUNTING)
- (CROWD SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING CONTINUES)
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
(PRISONER SPEAKING ENGLISH)
Boxing.
(SPEAKING THAI)
(ALL LAUGHING)
(YELLING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
I wanna bet. Cigarette.
(MAN SPEAKING ENGLISH)
BILLY: Two packs.
(SPEAKING THAI)
(ALL CHATTERING)
(ALL CHEERING)
Two packs.
Come on, hey.
Two packs. Cigarettes.
- No.
- My fucking fish won.
(SPEAKING THAI)
My fish won.
Give me two packs
of cigarettes.
I fucking won, man.
I fucking won.
- Fucking...
- (GLASS SHATTERS)
(SPEAKING THAI)
(BOSS SPEAKING THAI)
(IN ENGLISH) Hey.
- (BOTH CHUCKLING)
- No, no, no. Fighting fish.
- I won a bet.
- Okay.
No. No girlfriend.
I wanted
to apologize actually,
because I lied to you
about me dad.
Not having a family.
I've got a dad,
I've got brothers.
They don't know I'm in prison.
Why are you in here anyway?
Why?
(LAUGHS)
Sorry.
(ALL GRUNTING)
BILLY: Put 'em up. Put 'em up.
Put 'em up! Come on!
Put 'em up.
(BOTH SPEAKING THAI)
BILLY: Go on.
Just fucking do it.
Eh? One, two.
(BOTH SPEAKING THAI)
(COACH SPEAKING ENGLISH)
(SPEAKING THAI)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey!
Fucking go!
- (BILLY SHOUTING)
- (ALL CLAMORING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(SPEAKING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(CROWD CHANTING)
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
(BELL DINGING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(REFEREE SPEAKING
IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(TRADITIONAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(REFEREE SPEAKING THAI)
- (BOTH GRUNTING)
- (CROWD SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(SNIFFLES)
(COACH SPEAKING
IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(REFEREE SPEAKING
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(REFEREE SPEAKING THAI)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(PANTING)
(REFEREE SPEAKING THAI)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(MAN SPEAKING THAI)
(GRUNTING)
(MEN SPEAKING THAI)
(BILLY LAUGHING)
(MONK CHANTING
IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(IN ENGLISH)
I can.
- I wanna fight.
- Good.
Thank you, sir.
Oh.
(SPEAKING THAI)
- (SPEAKING THAI)
- (BILLY SPEAKING ENGLISH)
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(INAUDIBLE)
(SPEAKING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
- Three?
- (CONTINUES IN THAI)
(IMITATES GUNSHOT)
(BILLY EXHALING SHARPLY)
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
(TATTOOIST CHANTING
IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(COUNTING
(SPEAKING THAI)
- (COUNTING IN THAI)
- (GRUNTING)
(COUNTING IN THAI)
(SPEAKING THAI)
- (COUNTING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
- (BILLY GRUNTING)
(SPEAKING THAI)
(GRUNTING)
(PRISONER SPEAKING
IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(PRISONER GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MOANING)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
OVER PA)
(GUARD SPEAKING THAI)
(ALL SHOUTING)
(SPEAKING THAI)
(PANTING)
BILLY: Fame.
- Fame.
- (IN ENGLISH)
(SPEAKING THAI)
What the fuck are you doing?
You move fast, don't you?
I'm not fucking
talking to you!
You fucking piss me off.
You fucking wanna go?
You wanna fucking go?
You're boring. You're boring.
You're a fucking liar.
- You're boring.
- I don't lie!
You're a fucking liar!
(SNIFFLES)
(GRUNTING ANGRILY)
I said fucking hit me.
(SPEAKING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
Come on, fucking hit me.
Fucking hit me, come on.
Fucking hit me.
Fucking hit me then, eh?
Fucking hit me, eh?
(GRUNTING)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
Fucking gloves.
(SPEAKING THAI)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(EXHALES)
(GRUNTS)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(PANTING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(MONKS CHANTING
IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(SPEAKING THAI)
(DOOR LOCKS)
(ALL SHOUTING
IN THAI)
(SPEAKING THAI)
Lek, I'm sorry.
Lek, I'm sorry, okay?
I fucked up.
I made a mistake.
Lek, I'm fucking sorry.
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
- (COUNTING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
- (GRUNTING)
(SPEAKING THAI)
(COUNTING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
One-two, One-two, one-two.
Okay, push-up.
(BOXERS COUNTING
IN THAI)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SPEAKING THAI)
(ALL LAUGHING)
(ALL CHEERING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(FAME SPEAKING ENGLISH)
(FAME SINGING IN THAI)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SPEAKING THAI)
(GRUNTING)
(COACH SPEAKING THAI)
COACH: One, two.
(GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
Okay.
Hey, Billy.
(SPEAKING THAI)
I'm gonna get
your money, all right?
I'm gonna get it.
I've got a fight coming up.
I'm gonna win, okay?
I'm gonna win. I'm gonna fight.
I'm gonna fucking win,
all right?
I'm gonna fucking win, okay?
(BILLY GRUNTING)
(BILLY SCREAMING)
I'm gonna get the money
for you, all right?
I'm gonna win the fight.
(MEN SPEAKING THAI)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(SPEAKING THAI)
I'm okay.
(VOMITING)
(SHIVERING)
I've got a tournament
coming up.
It's all I've got.
DOCTOR: The reason why
you have a rupture
is because of boxing
and the massive abuse
of drugs and alcohol.
Any more trauma, and frankly,
you could bleed to death.
(SIGHS) Look, Mr. Moore,
I'm sorry.
I'll keep me guard up.
(INAUDIBLE)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
ON PA)
(BREATHING SHARPLY)
(GROANING)
(ANNOUNCER SPEAKING THAI)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(CROWD BOOING)
(TRADITIONAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
Okay?
Yeah.
(SPEAKING THAI)
(BELL DINGS)
(TRADITIONAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(CROWD SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(GRUNTING)
(REFEREE SPEAKING THAI)
(GROANS)
(CROWD SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(GRUNTING)
(BELL DINGS)
(CROWD BOOING)
(MEN ARGUING IN THAI)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
COACH: Okay?
(GROANING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SPEAKING THAI)
(TRADITIONAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ALL CHEERING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(VOMITING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(ALL SHOUTING IN THAI)
(SIREN WAILING)
(BEEPS)
Hello?
(DOOR OPENS)
(NURSE SPEAKING
IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(CONVERSING IN THAI)
(WOMAN SPEAKING THAI)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(CHILDREN SHOUTING)
(PANTING)
(EXHALES)
(GUARD SPEAKING THAI)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER
OVER RADIO)
(SPEAKING THAI)
(GUARD SPEAKING
IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
Subtitle By: explosiveskull
& Improved By: Fidel33
Sub Upload Date: July 22, 2018